# Valentino Yudhistira Jehaut

Denpasar, Bali, Indonesia



valenjehaut@tutanota.com



linkedin.com/in/valenj



081353682227



https://valenjehaut.vercel.app

## Summary

Currently as an undergraduate student pursuing Double Bachelor's Degree in Information Systems (S.SI) at ITB Stikom Bali & Information Technology (BIT (Hons)) at HELP University, Malaysia. As a student, I always try to myself step ahead and risking to try to pursue new things and challenges.

I've been Web Developer for more than 2 years & an UI/UX Designer for more than a year. I started to pursue in this job title since Vocabulary High School until now. With the total combined experience of more than 3 years. I'll always try to catch up with the current trends but also at the same time make my skills more mature. Some of the skills that I've got at the time is that I'm able to make a Full-Stack websites using the latest technology.

One of main achievement is that i got a chance to join an International Hackathon Event by Asia Europe Foundation and experience an amazing experience within the event and our team. And the impact of it within myself is that I've try to make myself much more ambitious to pursue my dreams and my passion.

## **Experience**



### 같 UI/UX Designer

#### Bendega

Oct 2021 - Present (1 year +)

I've started to work here as an intern for a month and now as a part-time employee. My task that I'm currently manage are as follows:

- 1. Make a new website for them with their IT team using Figma as the main design tool and ReactJS as the main Front-end of the Website (Click here: bendega.id).
- 2. Joining various events and representing as Bendega at those events (Inkuri, CCL Changemakers)
- 3. Currently designing another website for one of their products with other members of the IT Team (Mangrove Reborn)



#### Web Developer

#### Bali Mountain Retreat

Jul 2021 - Present (1 year 3 months +)

One of my main tasks in Bali Mountain Retreat is as follows:

- 1. Redesign their previous incomplete website (As they stated before I got employed) to more "complete" looking website using Wordpress as the CMS, Elementor as the main Website Builder, Yoast SEO to ensure that the SEO is always up-to-date, and Litespeed Cache as the main acceleration plugin to make sure that the website is fast and responsive).
- 2. Maintaining their website to ensure that their website's content is updated.
- 3. Managing their Channel Manager (Cloudbeds) to ensure that the room prices, details, photos, and etc are always updated across all travel online booking platforms.



## **Hackathon Team Member (ASEFSU23)**

### Asia-Europe Foundation (ASEF)

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

I got selected as a participant at an Online Hackathon Event called 23rd ASEF Summer University from Asia-Europe Foundation (Intergovernmental, Not-for-profit Organization). At the hackathon, I was assigned to the Bangladesh Team 4 and got a role as UI/UX Developer my tasks were as follows:

- 1. Making the website's wireframe and the sitemap of the business idea (Ekhane) using Miro as the main virtual collaboration platform.
- 2. Designing the website using Figma as the main design tool.
- 3. Making the site live using Angular. Js as the Front-end Javascript Framework and Tailwind as the Front-end UI Framework with the IT Team.

## PHP Programmer

Pt kriya jaya internasional Jan 2019 - Mar 2019 (3 months)

### **Education**

### **HELP University**

Bachelor of Information Technology - B.IT Sep 2021 - Sep 2024

## 💧 Institut Teknologi dan Bisnis STIKOM Bali

Information Technology
Sep 2021 - Sep 2024
Currently as an undergraduate at ITB Stikom Bali

## SMK TI Bali Global Denpasar

Software Engineering, Computer Programming/Programmer, General Jul 2017 - Jun 2021

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- Junior Web Developer Balai Diklat Industri Denpasar
- **UI/UX Design Trainee** Balai Diklat Industri Denpasar

#### Skills

English • Web Design • Web Development • HTML5 • PHP • Figma (Software) • Microsoft Visual Studio Code • WordPress • Microsoft Word • React.js